{
    "id": "2b529601532e45939000ff0f3da73226",
    "title": "General Vocabulary Exercise",
    "questions": [
        {
            "question": "Ants love to eat …………………………",
            "description": "A currant is a small berry used in buns.",
            "answers": [
                "currents",
                "currants"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "f860e8238a7846d6822fe2258d6a58d6"
        },
        {
            "question": "……………………………. fashions are more casual than those of the 1960’s.",
            "description": "Current means present day.",
            "answers": [
                "Current",
                "Currant"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "dabf50b53c0740dbbc8a433fbec872ca"
        },
        {
            "question": "He gave the report a ……………………………… glance and tossed it aside.",
            "description": "A cursory glance is a quick glance.",
            "answers": [
                "curt",
                "cursive",
                "cursory"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "bc13401425f549adb29af4b36654fd11"
        },
        {
            "question": "He arrived with his ………………………………. promptness.",
            "description": "Customary means habitual or usual. ",
            "answers": [
                "customary",
                "customery",
                "custodial"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "249975ef7a454316b09954e48bde2e51"
        },
        {
            "question": "The nation must put a …………………………. on its spending to balance the economy.",
            "description": "As a noun curb means restraint or control.",
            "answers": [
                "curb",
                "curtail",
                "hindrance"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "8a763c914cd44976a45b35078562e448"
        },
        {
            "question": "His loss didn’t …………………………….. his zest for living.",
            "description": "As a verb damp can mean reduce, diminish or depress. Dampen means the same.",
            "answers": [
                "damp",
                "dampen",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 2,
            "id": "dfc72a90cd4f4f1a9d74c9fa0452e2d0"
        },
        {
            "question": "With that …………………………… outlook he does not trust anyone.",
            "description": "Cynical means scornful, derisive or sarcastic.",
            "answers": [
                "cynical",
                "clinical"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "83b66989bde94fdab98c295311ce8461"
        },
        {
            "question": "The negotiations reached a …………………………. after two hours.",
            "description": "All of these words mean the same.",
            "answers": [
                "deadlock",
                "standoff",
                "impasse",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "a5532b741df74a608a18a1f07d9fdd67"
        },
        {
            "question": "The boy’s directions ……………………….. us, and we never did find the lake.",
            "description": "To mislead someone is to give them false information unintentionally or unknowingly.",
            "answers": [
                "misled",
                "deceived",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "13f254747265446ab8c8439729ea9228"
        },
        {
            "question": "She ……………………………. her fiancé by dating others.",
            "description": "To deceive someone is to give them a false impression either knowingly or intentionally.",
            "answers": [
                "misled",
                "deceived",
                "Either could be used here"
            ],
            "correct": 1,
            "id": "21bb6e07516846bba1f1182f37316b13"
        },
        {
            "question": "The magazine doesn’t accept any ……………………………. ads.",
            "description": "",
            "answers": [
                "deceitful",
                "deceptive",
                "misleading",
                "All of the above"
            ],
            "correct": 3,
            "id": "355aa594378c4466b617d4cd37f57c66"
        },
        {
            "question": "From her conversation, I …………………………. that she had a large family.",
            "description": "Deduce means conclude or comprehend.",
            "answers": [
                "deduced",
                "deducted"
            ],
            "correct": 0,
            "id": "0ed4b19c817d468ea1500e455020b3a9"
        }
    ]
}